<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Pro Dev</string>
  <string name="app_title">Pro Dev!</string>
  <string name="golden_circles_title">Golden Circles!</string>
  <string name="golden_circles_date">6/18/2018</string>
  <string name="golden_circles_text">
    Hi, I\'m Nick.  I love interface design and development because I love actualizing the power of great code.  I\'m doing this through native mobile app development and front-end development.  Have you worked on something related to UI/UX?\n\n
    Hi, my name\'s Nick.  I love learning new technologies because I love building things in new and improved ways.  Right now I\'m learning Spring, Java, Android and Rest APIs.  Do you have any cool internships where I could get some hands on experience in a popular new technology?\n\n
    Hey, Nick LoCicero!  I\'m creating helping get better technology in the hands of small businesses because it can make a big difference to local communities in both economic development and community happiness.  I\'m taking the Deepdive Coding Bootcamp in Java-Android-Salesforce and making my own projects to learn these skills.  Do you know of a small business that wants to collaborate and implement some awesome tech for its customers and community?
  </string>
  <string name="qualitative_quantitative_title">Quantitative ~ Qualitative</string>
  <string name="qualitative_quantitative_date">6/18/2018</string>
  <string name="qualitative_quantitative_text">
    3 Quantitative Accomplishments of mine:\n
    \t\tI am at level Captain on CodeFights and have won over 70 tournaments\n
    \t\tI amm trained by the SPCA to help abused animals learn to trust people again\n
    \t\tI have reviewed over 800 Udacity Student Projects for Full-stack Web Dev and Android Nanodegrees\n\n

    3 Qualities I Possess:\n
    \t\tExpressive, enjoy the process of expressing ideas and ideas in general (may philosophize too much =P)\n
    \t\tCurious, makes it easy to learn things (can fall down Wikipedia rabbit holes)\n
    \t\tThorough, love spending time in the state of flow, creating (not too attentive to deadlines)\n\n

    I am definitely more Right Brained, however I am much more cerebral than limbic.  I enjoy the state of flow.  That creativity and being in the moment is awesome!\n\n
  </string>
</resources>
