<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Pro Dev</string>
  <string name="pro_dev">Pro Dev!</string>
  <string name="prodev_learn">Pro-dev feedback. I was working with the team and it was great to
    play the forbidden island game with the mindset how do I impact the team. I have learned so
    far it’s best to pretend I’m playing basketball with my team. Since this is an intellectual
    venture, highly creative, it’s easy to want to manage things. But in basketball I work to help
    set things up for others to score points, and try to keep a general team camaraderie for fun
    and recreation. Anyway, I am learning that sometimes it’s best for me to take something and
    get it done and the check back in with the team to see how I can help. That way things grow
    organically rather than me trying to help with everything. Am I supposed to add that to the
    prodev android app? The doing things and taking initiative is like driving for a layup, myself.
    But I also don’t run over to a teammate hen he’s shooting and help him shoot his or her basket.
    All I should do is encourage him to take the shot, which makes it much easier for him to feel
    confident and do something wholeheartedly without having to worry about someone else hoping he
    gets it right or now. Less pressure and more results.\n\nThe demo day (well, demo evening) was great! I feel so charged and energized by it. :) I met many great people. Dan said to me, Nick, my brain is just too fried to answer any of your questions right now. But, go ask Sebastian. He can tell you. So, I did! And guess what! I began my question. My quest is driven by the question: How do employeers make the decision to hire someone? This question is very tricky because it is not about what makes them make the decision or why they make the decision. It\'s deeper than that. Dan is like the sensei. He knew to tell me, Nick, this question is the answer to your journey. I learned last night that every journey can only be answered by question. An answer always ends a journey unless it asks another question. Thanks to Dan being mysterious and helping me see that it is the journey that I am embarking on and that it gives me something to talk about and search for when I network, I know I will have a lot to say and questions to ask and be curious about. Sometimes I get nervous at mixers and events because I don\'t know what to say, but thanks to this insight, I now see that having a question can lead me into a mysterious journey at an event and take me to the place I am searching for. Have a question, don\'t have an answer. Also, one person says he hires people not skills. He doesn\'t hire skills and put them in a closet to do their thing. He hires people who can communicate and work on a team. People that can learn and have skills. But not necessarily skills, *people* who have skills. So that was good, but best of all, it\'s the question that drives us and allows us to do things at the mixers and networking events.</string>
</resources>
